[{"answer": "No, I'm not.", "docId": "111012pmt", "aSentId": 10, "question": "You're not implacably opposed to running for president?", "qSentId": 9}, {"answer": "I mean, look, this is a time to serve.", "docId": "111012pmt", "aSentId": 13, "question": "Could America be ready for another Bush in the White House?", "qSentId": 12}, {"answer": "Well, I didn't see it because I was flying out to San Francisco, but this morning, bright and early, I saw what other people thought of the debate.", "docId": "111012pmt", "aSentId": 22, "question": "And what did you think of last night?", "qSentId": 21}, {"answer": "He's very consistent.", "docId": "111012pmt", "aSentId": 31, "question": "I mean he's -- he's consistent, isn't he?", "qSentId": 30}, {"answer": "Well, I don't have as much weight behind me as Chris Christie, but I'm getting up there.", "docId": "111012pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "Are you prepared to do this?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "I think I have a sense of history, for starters.", "docId": "111012pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "What should America be doing -- what should American politicians be doing?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "Oh, yes, absolutely.", "docId": "111012pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "You support their right to protest?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "Well, we do that all the time, but not in this particular case.", "docId": "111012pmt", "aSentId": 106, "question": "So we should blame your brother, basically?", "qSentId": 105}, {"answer": "You know, I think -- I think our banks are stronger today than they were in September of 2008, and they're certainly stronger in terms of their capital ratios compared to the European banks.", "docId": "111012pmt", "aSentId": 123, "question": "Do you feel confident that enough is being done to prevent that?", "qSentId": 122}, {"answer": "It feels -- when you travel to Asia, particularly, you know, you get this spirit of optimism that's quite remarkable, and also a feeling that they look at us and kind of say, you know, poor older brother, you know, your days are behind you.", "docId": "111012pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "Do you think it's kind of anti the culture of the country?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "Well, I think I learned it at my mama's knee to start with.", "docId": "111012pmt", "aSentId": 154, "question": "Why has education always been your great passion?", "qSentId": 153}, {"answer": "It's very frightening.", "docId": "111012pmt", "aSentId": 164, "question": "Quite frightening, isn't it?", "qSentId": 163}, {"answer": "Look, I think -- I think our country has rested on its laurels.", "docId": "111012pmt", "aSentId": 179, "question": "Why has nobody really got to grits with this?", "qSentId": 178}, {"answer": "Well, today, it's anywhere from 8 to 10 percent.", "docId": "111012pmt", "aSentId": 199, "question": "And how much should be driven from the state?", "qSentId": 198}, {"answer": "Where it is today is fine in terms of the relevance of education.", "docId": "111012pmt", "aSentId": 203, "question": "What do you think is the optimum?", "qSentId": 202}, {"answer": "A focus on early childhood literacy, so the children come prepared to learn.", "docId": "111012pmt", "aSentId": 213, "question": "What are the key, simple ways that other states, and therefore America, collectively, can get to grips with this corrosive education system?", "qSentId": 212}, {"answer": "This is like one of those fights in the previous segment, I believe, that we're -- that it's the transition from kind of the old '70s way of doing things to the 21st century way of doing things.", "docId": "111012pmt", "aSentId": 230, "question": "Do even teachers' unions get this, do you think, or is this still, again, a very old-fashioned sense of what a union should be doing?", "qSentId": 229}, {"answer": "Well, Florida's an incredible -- it's purple, it's very purple.", "docId": "111012pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "What's the trick to being successful in Florida, if you're a Republican candidate right now?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "It's different.", "docId": "111012pmt", "aSentId": 268, "question": "What's it like having a brother and a dad who have both been president of the United States?", "qSentId": 267}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "111012pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "Do you have to have that ability to cope with huge pressure, but also have the family, the balance?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "And we didn't talk about it.", "docId": "111012pmt", "aSentId": 292, "question": "Well, that's an extraordinary thing to witness, isn't it?", "qSentId": 291}, {"answer": "I would say in the second term, the turning against him because of the war was difficult.", "docId": "111012pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "What was the toughest things for you to do?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111012pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "Was that the right thing to do?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "I'm sure he misses the White House, misses the service.", "docId": "111012pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "Does he miss being president?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "Well, because it's personal.", "docId": "111012pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "Why not personally?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "I can --", "docId": "111012pmt", "aSentId": 404, "question": "ORGAN: Can you see yourself running in the future?", "qSentId": 403}, {"answer": "No, it isn't.", "docId": "111012pmt", "aSentId": 406, "question": "Isn't it like a calling for you Bushes now?", "qSentId": 405}, {"answer": "That's pure -- that's just hypothetical, so I can't answer.", "docId": "111012pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "Could you see the situation where the personal reasons, which I won't press you on -- but where those would go away enough for you to consider running perhaps in 2016?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "No, I'm not.", "docId": "111012pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "You're not implacably opposed to running for president?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "Let's move to digital learn.", "docId": "111012pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "You don't just imagine one day just walking into the Oval Office?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "This is a scoop.", "docId": "111012pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "Is this a scoop?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "I believe that passionately.", "docId": "111012pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "Some of this, Governor Bush, does modern technology help kids learn better and faster than the old-fashioned technology?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "I think --", "docId": "111012pmt", "aSentId": 471, "question": "What is your view about competition, whether it's sporting or academic, in schools in America?", "qSentId": 470}, {"answer": "I am.", "docId": "111012pmt", "aSentId": 473, "question": "Are you in favor of egg and spoon races?", "qSentId": 472}, {"answer": "I think he's wrong.", "docId": "111012pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "What do you think, Governor Bush?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "I happen to think -- I agree with Warren Buffett on the taxes.", "docId": "111012pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "Governor Wise?", "qSentId": 519}, {"answer": "I think during eight years, I've probably -- I'm going to be off a little bit, probably 50 people.", "docId": "111012pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "Do you know how many people you both executed?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111012pmt", "aSentId": 551, "question": "If you had the decision, if you were the president of the United States, would you try now and stop the death penalty?", "qSentId": 550}, {"answer": "ISE: Because DNA is modern technology.", "docId": "111012pmt", "aSentId": 563, "question": "How are you going to link it to education?", "qSentId": 562}, {"answer": "Consistently higher graduation rates.", "docId": "111012pmt", "aSentId": 569, "question": "Let me ask you first, Governor Bush?", "qSentId": 568}]